Guide to the Stanford University, Center for Latin American Studies, Records SC0185
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-1985-099
  - Mexico Course, 1979 spring (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Outreach (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Fulbright Interviews (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Fulbright Awards, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Ford Report, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Budget - NDEA, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - NDEA - Curriculum Development (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - NDEA - Outreach, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - NDEA - Library (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - North-South Center (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - NDEA - working papers, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rose Hayden - correspondence, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Scott Palmer - FSI (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Hills Brothers Coffee - Kenneth Jones (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - FLAS, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - State Dept. Meeting, 1976 Oct 18-19 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Bill Luers (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - LASA (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - North-South Center (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - WARO National Council rejection (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Warren Christopher - correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Terence Todman - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Fulbright Info, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Inter-American Fdn. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Woodrow Wilson Inst. for Scholars LA Program (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - UF/MG Position (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Albert B. Wenzell - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Fausto/Murilo visit, 1981 May (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - UERJ Internship Idea - Jacob Dolinger (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Bernal Flores (Costa Rica) Tinker (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Wanderlay Guilherme do Santos - Tinker Chair (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Jose Carlos Sebe Bom Meihy - Tinker (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Damian Bayon - Tinker Chair (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Jaime Serra - Tinker Chair (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Jean Franco and Other Personnel - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Karlene Dickey (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Francisco Orrego Vicuna (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Bolivar House News (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Curriculum Commission [Dr. Eugene Tucker] (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Summer Research Program - LAS (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - SOCCIS (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Archival and Manuscript Materials (Box 2)
  - Latin American Area Studies - new approaches (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Al Bildner - correspondence (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 2)
  - FRI 261 Winter Qtr. Exams, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 2)
  - International Material (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 2)
  - Films (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 2)
  - Film Series, 1974-1975 Winter Quarter (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 2)
  - Political Economy of Finance Workshop (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Migration Issues (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - University Fundraising Guidelines (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Title VI - Funding Cuts, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - SLABS - Replies, Questionaire 2nd Annual Direetory (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 2)
  - Poli Sci 116W (Van Whiting) Course Reserve, Winter Quarter, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1-24)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 3)
  - Films: Latin American (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Brazilian Films (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 3)
  - Johnson Foundation (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Phelps - Stokes Fund (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - SU Report of Gifts and Grants (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - LAS Gift Opportunities (GSO), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Brazilian Embassy (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - State Department (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - World Affairs Council (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Tinker Postdoctoral Fellowship - Erica Bruce's visit (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Revised Proposal Visiting Professorship - Tinker Foundation (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Tinker Foundation - Endowed Professorship (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Summer Grants for Graduate Students (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Summer Grants Applications, Graduate and Undergraduate (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Request for Funds - outside of usual categories, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Faculty Research Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Private Sector (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - LAS - Tinker Foundation (Martha Muse), 1974 Jun 25 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Tinker Foundation (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Tinker Foundation, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Rolando Perez Tinker Centro Para Investigaciones Historicas En La Argentina (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Tinker Fellows (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Campaign for Stanfoxd / Gift Opportunity, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Cento para investigaciones historicas en la argentina (Box 3)
  - NF Tinker Grant Proposal (Box 3)
  - Joint Medical Sehool LAS Degree (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Joint Center Coordinator Search, 1981 Aug-Sep (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Secretary II Title VI, 1981 Sep (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - LAS Secretary II Requisition End Posting, 1977 Jun 21 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Placement Service (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - FLAS Fellowships, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - FLAS Recipients, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - FLAS Continuation, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Grad. Fellowships for Area Students, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - California State Graduate Fellowships (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Coordinating Committee for Study Abroad at Sao Paulo (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fulbright - Hays Grad. Student Fellowships (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fulbright - International Exchange of Scholars (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - OAS Fellowship (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Strengthening of Portuguese Progtam, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Vortice - Spanish and Portuguese Journal (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Guide - Cost and info update (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Tape Reel (Box 4)
  - LAS Center Labels (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Manual for Guide and Labels (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Original - S-B Guide, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Unfiled Material (Box 4)
- Additional Records, Accession ARCH-2010-087
  - Indices to MA Theses, organized by year., 1976-2007 (Box 1)
- Additional Records, circa 1985-2005; Accession ARCH-2010-106
  - Public Programs, 1991-1999; Subseries 1
    - Original Fliers/documents for events during Fall 1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Original Fliers/documents for events during Winter 1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Original Fliers/documents for events during Spring 1999 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Events co-sponsored 1998-1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Lunch Seminar with Ricardo Letts 6/22/1999 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Brazilian Cultural Week May 1-8 1999 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Fliers/documents for events during Spring 1999 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Chile in the Next Century Panel 4/15/1999 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Event: Eduardo Montealegre (Nicaraguan Foreign Minister) 5/6/99 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Jorge Arrate (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Luncheon with Beatriz Sarlo 2/23/99 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - BBL with Torcuato di Tella 2/10/99 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Event with Julia Lopez of the Rockefeller Foundation 1/13/1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Latin American Film Conference May 97 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Cuauhtemoc Cardenas November 1997 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Event with Leticia Singer 2/1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Events co-sponsored 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Carlos Andres Perez, Venezuelan President visit to Bolivar House, 6 May 1991 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Tet Ansanm’s Volunteer project in Haiti 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Mexico Conference 11/13 – 11/15, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Branca Moreira Alves Event May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Ballet Folklorico Concert/Reception 5/22/98 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Master’s Events Flyers Spring 98 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Spring Programs 1998 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Isabel Duque Saberi Event May 1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Fernando Birri Event May 98 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Elena Poniatowska Event April 1998 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Guadalupe Rivera April 98 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Vilmar Faria January 98 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Brazilian Writer in Residence: Raduan Nassar 2/98 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Colombian Ambassador – Esguerra Event 3/19/98 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Alkimar Moura Event March 1998 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Sarukhan Seminar Winter 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Sebastiao Salgado Photo Exhibit 1998 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Salgado Exhibit Captions (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - Flyer Masters Winter 98 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Winter Programs 1998 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Fall 1997 Original Flyers (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Fall Programs 1997 (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Winter Fiesta 1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Ambassador Silva-Herzog 9/29/97 (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Lula Da Silva Speaking tour 1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Benedita da Silva Fall 1997 Nov. 3 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Spring 1997 – Flyer for Masters Events (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Tet Ansanm’s Volunteer project in Haiti 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Events co-sponsored by CLAS 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Luiz Felipe Lampreia (Brazilian Foreign Minister) Event (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Luiz Felipe Lampreia Event 6/97 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Joao Almino Farewell event 6/3/97 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Events Spring 97 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Esteban Moctezuma Event 5/19/97 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Javier Elorriaga/Zapatista talk 2/7/97 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Ana Mirando – Brazilian Writer in Residence Feb 97 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - RYSE Workshop Feb 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Benedito dos santos 2/25/97 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - From Frei to frei Conference Spring 97 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Flyer Masters Winter 97 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Events Winter 97 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Events Fall96 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Hilton Homecoming Reception 10/12/96 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Flyer Masters – Fall 1996 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Inti Illimani 11/15/96 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Event: War Crimes and War Criminals Oct 10-12 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Brazil Conference “Negotiating Rights” Oct 96 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Chile: Facts and figures Information on Eduardo Frei (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Chile Conference CVs of participants (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Chile Conference – Final papers (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Chile Conference Proofs 4/97 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Chile Conference: Draft papers (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Extra Paper copies: Chile conference (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Chile Conference Public Requests (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Cinco de mayo 1997/ Spring fest 1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - From frei to frei: Perspectives on chile April 24-26 1997 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Grassroots voices: Natl movement of street children 25 Feb 1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Brazilian Writers panel Feb 21, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Iberian History Workshop 26-28 Jan 1997 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Brazilian conference 1996 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Conference on Comparative Economic Development fall1996 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Conference on Mexico Nov. 1997 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Brazil Rights conference Oct 1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Symposium on Race Relations Nov 1998 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1995-1996 Bag Lunch Flyers (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Events sponsored and co-sponsored Spring 1996 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Haiti Program Summer 1996 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Commencement 1996 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Laura Paull, Havana Nagila Event 5/1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Spring Fiesta 5/16/1996 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Events May 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Ecuador Round Table 4/12/1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Allan Nairn April 24, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Chiapas Photo Exhibit Feb/March 1996 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - UCB Stanford Symposium 1996 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Events April 1996 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Events Spring 1996 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - His Excellency Fernando Henrique Cardoso (Brazilian President) Event Logistics March 96 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Dinkelspiel Seating (Cardoso Event) 3/11/96 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Brazil Roundtable (Cardoso Event) 3/11/96 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Events March/96 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Roman Chalbaud Event April 8-13 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - February 1996 Events (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Mexico Symposium (North America Forum) Feb. 9, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - January 1996 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Guillermo O’Donnnel cancelled event Feb. 1996 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Ciro Gomes Event Nov. 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Events November 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Events October 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Human Rights Workshop Oct. 3-4 1995 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Visit by Francisco Weffort (Brazilian Min. of Culture)10/1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Proposal Brazil Speakers Series April 1996 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Events Fall 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Human Rights Workshop Oct. 3-4 1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Open House 10/10/1995 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - M.A. Orientation 9/26/95 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Pres. Cardoso Photos 3/11/96 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Ciro Gomes Nov. 95 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Mexico Symposium feb. 96 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Human Rights symposium Oct. 95 Proof Sheets (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Misc. Photos 95-96 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Photos 95-96 fall - April (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Bag Lunch Series 1994-1995 Originals (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Commencement 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Sponsored and Co-sponsored events Spring 95 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Haiti Trip 1995 (Tet Ansanm / H. Schmidt) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Amigo Reception 6/27/95 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Spring Fiesta 5/18/95 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Venezuelan Ambassador Echeverria 5/8/95 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Chilean Ambassador J. Biehl 4/6/95 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - May 1995 Speakers (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - April 95 Speakers (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Barbara Trent Event 94 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - March 95 Speakers (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Alma Andina 1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Ruben Zamora Event Spring 95 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Eduardo Galeano Event Spring 95 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Alberto Quiros 3/16/95 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Madres de la Plaza de Mayo Event 3/3/95 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Jose Serra / Brazil Working Group 2/28/95 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Venezuela Trip 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Feb. 1995 Speakers (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - January 95 Speakers (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Open House 1994 10/13/94 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Diego Iztep Pasa Event 1994 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Pablo Gonzalez Casanova Event Nov 1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Peruvian Opening Exhibit/Reception November 94 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous / name tags 1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Nicario Jimenez Quispe, Retablo Artist Event Nov. 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Guatemalan Law Students (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - October 1994 Brown Bag Lunches (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - November Speakers (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Potential Speakers 94 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Potential Events 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - More Potential Speakers 93-94 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Miscellaneous Information 93-94 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Brown Bag Notes 1993-94 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Eduardo Galeano Photos / proof May 1995 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Miscellaneous Photos 94-95 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Photos Spring Fiesta 1995 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Ruben Zamora Proofs 4/17/1995 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Proofs – Lecture and Reception for Venezuelan Ambassador 5/95 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Proofs/Photos Chilean Ambassador 4/6/95 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Photos / Neg. Alma Andina Orion Spanish School Visit 4/26/95 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Proofs and Photos: Jose Serra 2/28/95 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Miscellaneous Photos Students 94-95 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Proofs: Alberto Quiros reception 3/16/95 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Proofs: Madres de Plaza de Mayo 3/3/95 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Proofs/negatives: Peruvian Retablo Exhibit Oct-Nov. 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous pictures 94 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Photos Events 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Photos Events 1991-1992 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Photos Events 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - InterActions Publications 92-94 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - IIS News Magazines – Upcoming issue 93-94 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Co-sponsored events 93-94 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Daniel Vigletti Event (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Lunch with Brazilian Ambassador 6/22/1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - 1993-1994 Undergrads (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Visiting Scholars/Fellows 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Master Students 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Speaker CVs (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Environmental Conference May 4th Mailing lists (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Environmental Conference May 4, 5 1994 Participants (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Environmental Conference – Facilities, Catering, Brochures (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Environmental Conference Reimbursements (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Coro Hispano de San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - May 1994 Speakers (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Justina Tzuc Chinol Event 1994 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Fiesta de Fin de Año 5/20/94 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - March/April 1994 Speakers (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - April 26th Poetry Event (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Aristide (Haitian President) Event Feb 1994 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Aristide Caterers (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Speaker Fausto Guimaraes Event (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - February 1994 Speakers + Calendar Masters (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Haroldo Dilla Event Feb. 1994 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Photos Events 1994 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Brazilian / Mexican Poets Jan 26 1994 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - January 94 Speakers Calendar Masters (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Afro Cuban Music Performace Nov 4, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Institute for International Studies Advisory Council Information (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Information on Guatemalan Painter Sept 1993 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Faculty Colloquium (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Women Speakers (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - From Corporatism to Neo-liberalism: Business Modernizers in Brazil by Peter Kingstone. Oct 13, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Open House 1993 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Evangelina Rodriguez Lopez Event Oct. 1993 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Immigration Panel May 1991 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - International Women’s Media Foundation Information (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Immigration Panel Reception Nov. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Immigration Panel Flyers 1993 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Fund Transfers 1992-1993 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Brown Bag Lunches Notes 92-93 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - June Reception 1993 – Guest List (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Musician/food info for June Reception 93 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Workshop on El Salvador Peace Accords 5/6-5/7 1992-93 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Roberta Lajous (Secretary of Intl Affairs for PRI in Mexico) 5/25/1993 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - “Brazil’s Street Children” 4/6-4/7/1993 (Box 6, Folder 910)
    - Environmental Seminar Series Spring 1993 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Environmental Seminar Series Spring 1993 (Payments) (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - “Luchando Ayer y Hoy: A Teatro Trilogy” 4/15/93 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Fernando Perez Correa: “Modernization and Adult Education in Mexico” Jan 1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Cecilia Vicuña: Chilean Performance Artist April 1993 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Alberto Ruy-Sanchez: “A Discussion of Mogrador” March 1993 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Rev. Bob Pelton C.S.C “Santo Domingo, 1992” (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Gabino Palomares (Mexican Guitarrist): “Mexico a traves de su canto” April 93 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Rafael Hernandez: “Cuban Political Developments in 1992” 1993 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - HIV in Cuba – Jan. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - KQED’s 10-part series “Americas” 1993 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Susan Cashion: “Racial Conflict and artistic expression in Puerto Rico” 01/93 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - HJK Knowles Grants Presentations 2/10/1993 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Ronald Wonnacott: “Hemisphere Trade Liberalization” 2/10/93 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Cort Worthington: “Unarmed Commitment” Feb. 93 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Friedrich Katz: “The Pancho Villa Movement in Mexico” 3/93 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Julio Cesar Montaño: “Afro Colombian Reality” Feb. 1993 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Gonzalo Farez: “Indigenous Movement in Ecuador” 93 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Bruce Harris: “They Shoot Children, Don’t they?” Nov. 92 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Eliseo Subiela (Argentine Filmmaker) –Event 1992 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Fernando Rospigliosi Nov. 1992 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Prof. Ben Paul: “San Pedro La Laguna” 1992 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - ENLACE’s 1993 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Argentine Art Exhibit (Sept. 1992) (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Brown Bag Lunches Spring 1992 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Speaker Bios Brown Bag Lunches - 1992 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Brown Bag lunch Series 1991-92 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - University Visitors 1991 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Co-sponsored Events 1992 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Conference Organized by Steve Haber (January 1992) (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Cuauhtemoc Cardenas Presentation (Feb 1992) (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Advisory Council Luncheon and Brazilian Ambassador Event 92 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Brazil Conference April 1992 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - LAS Press Clippings 1985-1991 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - SPICE (Stanford Program on International and Cross Cultural Education Stationery (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Salinas (Mexican President) Visit 9/91 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Tinker – Miscellaneous grants pre 1988 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Aristide Visit – 4/94 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Cuban Dance Workshop 1991 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - US-Mexico Border Education Conference Oct 1991 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - UN Conference – El Salvador 1993 (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Brazil Seminar 1992 (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Intl Women’s Media Foundation 93/94 (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - Kausachum Cusco Movie 1991 (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Alfredo Cesar “Nicaragua Today” Oct 1992 (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - Liam Mahony Event 2/26/99 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Mayors Conference (Beth’s Notes and Names) 1/99 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Mayors Conference 1999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Mayors Conference Proofs (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Winter Events 1999 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Bios for Race Conference (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Race Relations Conference 11/3/98 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Isabel Parra 10/28/1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Rodolfo Stavenhagen Event 11/16/1998 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Edgar Rojas Event Minister of Health Ecuador (10/98) (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Ambassador Gelson Fonseca Oct 1998 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Eduardo Stein (Foreign Minister of Guatemala) 9/98 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Events Fall 1998 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Americas y Latinas (Journal of Women and Gender), 1992-1998; Subseries 2
    - Posters and Advertising for the journal (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Office of Student Affairs (OSA) authorization documents/ Public Board (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Cover Submission (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Americas and Latinas Budget (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Accepted Submissions (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Rejected Submissions (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Americas and Latinas Organization/Finances 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Old Submissions for Journal of Women and Gender in Latin America 1992 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Americas and Latinas Publication 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22-23)
    - Americas and Latinas Publication 1995 (Box 7, Folder 24-25)
    - Americas and Latinas Publication 1996 (Box 7, Folder 26-27)
    - Americas and Latinas Publication 1997– Copy 1 (Box 7, Folder 28-29)
    - Americas and Latinas Publication 1998– Copy 1 (Box 7, Folder 30-31)
    - Working groups 1993 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Speakers 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Resources 1995 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Printing Information (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Distribution of the journal Information (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Submissions (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Constitution of the group/ OSA (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Guest Speakers (Box 7, Folder 39)